{
    "subject": "resource/Princesse_Tam-Tam",
    "predicate": "property/director",
    "object": "resource/Edmond_T._Gr\u00e9ville",
    "human_readable": "The director of Princesse Tam-Tam is Edmond T. Gr\u00e9ville.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9591578841209412,
            "question": "Who is the director of Princesse Tam-Tam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.904116690158844,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Edmond T. Gr\u00e9ville?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8459770679473877,
            "question": "What is Edmond T. Gr\u00e9ville's background as a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8365852236747742,
            "question": "Is Edmond T. Gr\u00e9ville known for directing any other films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6645867228507996,
            "question": "Who are the main actors in Princesse Tam-Tam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6212493181228638,
            "question": "Where was Princesse Tam-Tam filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5125060677528381,
            "question": "What genre is Princesse Tam-Tam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4525836110115051,
            "question": "When was Princesse Tam-Tam released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44725388288497925,
            "question": "What are some of the themes explored in Princesse Tam-Tam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42564576864242554,
            "question": "How was Princesse Tam-Tam received by critics and audiences?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The director of Princesse Tam-Tam is Edmond T. Gr\u00e9ville.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1292_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the themes explored in Princesse Tam-Tam?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1292_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Princesse Tam-Tam released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1292_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is Princesse Tam-Tam?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1292_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1292_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1292_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1292_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1292_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1292_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1292_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1292_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1292_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1292_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1292_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that the director of Princesse Tam-Tam is indeed Edmond T. Gr\u00e9ville, as mentioned in multiple files (e.g., file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1292/re-ranker-msmarco/76.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe information provided in the documents clearly states that \"Princesse Tam-Tam\" was directed by Edmond T. Greville, which confirms the statement that Edmond T. Gr\u00e9ville is the director of Princesse Tam-Tam."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}